

Jesse Wells

designer + developer

jessewells.com/portfolio

About

Web Designer & Developer based in Brooklyn NY with 8+ years of work experience in graphic design, front-end design and front-end development

Likes

Vectors, SVG, Bezier Curves and Everything Scalable & Losless.

Web Components, Web Animation, Server Side Javascript.

PC, Microsoft, Adobe CC, Vue.js, Visual Studio Code, Pug, Stylus.

Contact

1263 Broadway Brooklyn NY 11221

jessenwells@gmail.com

347 243 5863



jessenwells



jessenwells

Work Experience

Modell's Sporting Goods Front-end Developer

2015 - current

Assisted in all areas to redesign and relaunch the new E-Commerce Website including migration of platforms from MarketLive to DemandWare.

Developed Automated and Streamlined Workflows, Site Specs, Style Guides and

Modern Email Templates.

Press Design

2010 - 2015

Lead Designer

Web Design, UI Design, Front-End Dev, Wordpress, Ecommerce, Web Ads, Print Design, Branding, Apparel

Graphics, Illustration, Print Ads.

Mammoth Advertising

2015 - 2016

Freelance

HTML5 Developer

Created animated interactive advertisments for web and display. Assisted in transition from flash to html5.

Everyday Media

2014 - 2015

Freelance

Digital Marketing Designer

Created and managed facebook ads. pages and weekly headers.

Social media promotional images. Print ads, web ads, and HTML emails.

F5 Interactive Agency

2012 - 2015

Freelance

Front-end Design and Development

Worked on various projects creating front end templates including complex UI, interactive data, infographics and large scale animations.

 \odot \odot \odot \bigcirc

 \odot \odot \odot \bigcirc

Education

Fashion Institute of Technology

BFA - Illustration

Skills

Adobe Illustrator	\odot \odot \odot \odot	HTML5/CSS3
Adobe Photoshop	\odot \odot \odot \odot	Javascript
Adobe InDesign	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	jQuery
Adobe After Effects	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Node.js
Adobe XD	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Vue.js
Wordpress	\odot \odot \odot \odot	Polymer
Woocommerce	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Angular
PHP/MySQL	\odot \odot \odot \bigcirc	Sass